Finding Aid for the George P. Johnson Negro Film Collection LSC.1042
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research Files
  - F
    - Fountaine, William
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 317-321, Halellujah. (Reel 5)
    - Four Feathers (Paramount, 1928); Frame(s) 704-707. (Reel 4)
    - Four for Texas (Warner Brothers, 1963); Frame(s) 1. (Reel 5)
    - Four Horseman of Apolcalpse, Frame(s) 2, 1921. (Reel 5)
    - Four Horsemen of Apolcalpse, Frame(s) 2, 1962. (Reel 5)
    - Four Shall Die (Million, 1938 & 1940); Frame(s) 3. (Reel 5)
    - Four Step Brothers
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 316, Carolina Blues. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 257, Greenwich Village; 513, Here Comes the Bride. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 112, Rhythm of the Island; 892-893, Step Brothers. (Reel 11)
    - Four Tones, Frame(s) 400, Harlem Rides the Range. (Reel 5)
    - Fourteen Hours, Frame(s) 4, Eric Portman. (Reel 5)
    - Fox in the Blue Town (Japanese), Frame(s) 6, Arthur Chico Lourant. (Reel 5)
    - Fox, John, Frame(s) 396. (Reel 9)
    - Foxes of Harrow (Fox, 1947)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 577, Mrs. A.C. Bilbrew. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 7-9. (Reel 5)
    - Foxx, Redd
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 269-284, Godfrey Cambridge. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 584, Fine Young Cannibals. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 10. (Reel 5)
    - Frances Goes to the Races (Universal, 1951); Frame(s) 11, Bill Walker. (Reel 5)
    - Francis of Assisi (Italian), Frame(s) 12. (Reel 4)
    - Francis, Vera (Viejah)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 13-15. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 690-692, The President's Lady; 713, The Prodigal. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 86. (Reel 12)
    - Franklin, Aretha
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 504, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 16-18. (Reel 5)
    - Franklin, Bo, Frame(s) 187-189, Gone With the Wind. (Reel 5)
    - Franklin, Irwin, Frame(s) 394, Harlem is Heaven. (Reel 5)
    - Franklin, Louise
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 42, Bright Road. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 19. (Reel 5)
    - Franklin, Wendell
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 234, Art of Love; 408, Band of Gold. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 498, Enter Laughing. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 20; 67 Funny Girl; 73, Gambit 239-241, Greatest Story Ever Told. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 743, The War Lords; 891, Who's Minding the Store. (Reel 12)
    - Fraulein (Fox, 1958); Frame(s) 21, James Edwards. (Reel 5)
    - Frazier, Dan, Frame(s) 22, Lord Love a Duck. (Reel 5)
    - Frazier, Dan
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 22, Lord Love a Duck. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 13, Lord Love a Duck. (Reel 8)
    - Frazier, Jamel, Frame(s) 23, Gene Autry, Tarzan. (Reel 5)
    - Frederick Douglass Film Company, Frame(s) 24-26. (Reel 5)
    - Frederick, Leon, Frame(s) 537. (Reel 9)
    - Frederick, Hal, Frame(s) 27. (Reel 5)
    - Frederick, Maxine, Frame(s) 127, The Incident. (Reel 6)
    - Free White & 21 (American, 1963); Frame(s) 46, Frederic O'Neal. (Reel 5)
    - Freed Alan
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 331-334, LaVerne Baker. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 333, Rock, Rock, Rock. (Reel 11)
    - Freedom (documentary, 1968); Frame(s) 28. (Reel 5)
    - Freedom Train, (1958); Frame(s) 29. (Reel 5)
    - Freeman, Al Jr.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 30-38. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 304-406, Negro actors. (Reel 9)
    - Freeman, Ernie, Frame(s) 39-45. (Reel 5)
    - Freeman, Kenneth, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - French Pictorial Service, Frame(s) 48-55. (Reel 5)
    - Frenchmens Creek (Paramount, 1944); Frame(s) 47, Billy Daniels. (Reel 5)
    - Friendly Persuasion (Allied Artist, 1955); Frame(s) 56. (Reel 5)
    - Friends of Distinction, Frame(s) 149. (Reel 2)
    - Frogs, Frame(s) 630. (Reel 4)
    - From Cotton Patch to Congress, Frame(s) 57. (Reel 5)
    - From Florence With Love, (1966); Frame(s) 58, Bill Cosby. (Reel 5)
    - Frontier Pony Express (Republic, 1939); Frame(s) 59, Noble Johnson. (Reel 5)
    - Frontier Scout (Grant Nat., 1938); Frame(s) 60, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 5)
    - Fugard, Athol, Frame(s) 411. (Reel 9)
    - Fullback, Frame(s) 394, Harlem is Heaven. (Reel 5)
    - Fuller, Curtis, Frame(s) 61, A Year Toward Tomorrow. (Reel 5)
    - Fuller, Gill, Frame(s) 62. (Reel 5)
    - Fuller, James, Frame(s) 253, Green Pastures. (Reel 5)
    - Fuller, Walter, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Fullwood, Yemiko
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 63-64, The Naked Ma ja. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 260-265, The Naked Ma ja. (Reel 9)
    - Funky Jazz (Japanese, 1960); Frame(s) 65. (Reel 5)
    - Funny Face (Paramount), Frame(s) 66, Harold Brown. (Reel 5)
    - Funny Girl (Columbia, 1967); Frame(s) 67. (Reel 5)
    - Fugua, Charlie, Frame(s) 146-147, Ink Spots. (Reel 6)
    - Fury of the Jungle (Columbia, 1934); Frame(s) 68, Clarence Muse. (Reel 5)
  - G
    - Gailliard, Slim
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 68-72; 185, Go, Man, Go; 498, Hell's A Poppin. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 175, Ovontie. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 904, Leory(Slam) Stewart. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 413, Two Joes from Brooklyn. (Reel 12)
    - Gaily, Gaily, Frame(s) 73. (Reel 5)
    - Gaines, Harris
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 241, Astor Pictures. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 74, The Betrayal. (Reel 5)
    - Gale, Wesley
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 72. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 304-306, Negro actors. (Reel 9)
    - Gallo, Loray, Frame(s) 73. (Reel 5)
    - Gambit, Frame(s) 74, William Franklin. (Reel 5)
    - Gambler from Natchez, Frame(s) 75. (Reel 5)
    - Gambling Boss of the Waterfront, Frame(s) 76, Arthur Chico Laurant. (Reel 5)
    - Gambling Ship, Frame(s) 77, Sam McDaniel. (Reel 5)
    - Games, Frame(s) 78, Ena Hartman. (Reel 5)
    - Gampu, Ken, Frame(s) 79. (Reel 5)
    - Gang Smashers, Frame(s) 81, Nina Mae McKinney. (Reel 5)
    - Gang War, Frame(s) 80, Ralph Cooper, et al. (Reel 5)
    - The Gangsters, Frame(s) 82, Dewey Robinson. (Reel 5)
    - Gangster on the Loose, Frame(s) 83, Ralph Cooper. (Reel 5)
    - Gangway for Tomorrow, Frame(s) 84, Sam McDaniel. (Reel 5)
    - Gans, Baby Joe (Gerald Slaughter), Frame(s) 85, death. (Reel 5)
    - Gant, Harry
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 86-87. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 255-279, Robert Levy; 327-715, Lincoln Motion Picture Company. (Reel 7)
    - Gantt, Hermann, Frame(s) 29. (Reel 3)
    - Garcia, Lea, Frame(s) 30, Black Orpheus. (Reel 3)
    - Gardell, Tess, Frame(s) 88. (Reel 5)
    - Gardner, Chappy, Frame(s) 149, International Negro Newsreel. (Reel 6)
    - Garland, Marcus, Frame(s) 89. (Reel 5)
    - Garner, Erroll
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 184. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 499, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 90. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 673, A New Kind of Love. (Reel 9)
    - Garrison, H.A. (Papa Slickum), Frame(s) 91; 317-321, Hallelujah. (Reel 5)
    - Garvey, Marcus, Frame(s) 10, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - The Gate City Feature Film Company, Frame(s) 92-94. (Reel 5)
    - Gateway Productions, Frame(s) 96, Bad Boy. (Reel 5)
    - Gateway to the Moon, Frame(s) 95, Noble Johnson. (Reel 5)
    - Gathering of the Eagles, Frame(s) 97, Robert Williams. (Reel 5)
    - Gay, John, Frame(s) 98, Lydia; 322, The Hallelujah Trail. (Reel 5)
    - Gaye, Marvin
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 99-100. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 744, The Motorcycle. (Reel 8)
    - Gayle, Rozell
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 579, Bikini Party. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 101 Bikini Party. (Reel 5)
    - Gee, Lottie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 66, Shuffle Along. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 102. (Reel 5)
    - The Geisha Boys, Frame(s) 103, Mimi Dillard. (Reel 5)
    - The Gene Krupa Story, Frame(s) 104, Mimi Dillard, Ruby Lane. (Reel 5)
    - General Film Company, Frame(s) 397, Ebony Film Corporation. (Reel 4)
    - General Spanky, Frame(s) 106, Houston informers. (Reel 5)
    - Genghis Khan, Frame(s) 105, Woody Strode. (Reel 5)
    - Gentle Julia, Frame(s) 107, The Guardian. (Reel 5)
    - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes, Frame(s) 108, Mildred Boyd, Carmen DeLavallade. (Reel 5)
    - George Randol Productions
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 373, Darktown Strutters Ball. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 110-112. (Reel 5)
    - George Washington Carver
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 181. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 111. (Reel 5)
    - George White Scandals, Frame(s) 108, Sam McDaniel, Edna Mae Johnson. (Reel 5)
    - George, Zelma, Frame(s) 109, An Educator Speaks. (Reel 5)
    - Georgia Rose
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 144-149, Aristo Films. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 50, Clarence Brooks. (Reel 2)
    - Ghost and the Guest, Frame(s) 108, Sam McDaniel. (Reel 5)
    - Ghost Breakers, Frame(s) 116, Willie Best, Noble Johnson. (Reel 5)
    - Ghost Hunt, Frame(s) 117, all Negro Cast. (Reel 5)
    - The Ghost of Tolston's Manor, Frame(s) 118. (Reel 5)
    - Ghost on the Loose, Frame(s) 120, Sammy Morrison. (Reel 5)
    - The Ghost Talks, Frame(s) 119, Steppin Fetchit. (Reel 5)
    - Giant, Frame(s) 121, Napoleon Whiting. (Reel 5)
    - Giant of his Race, Frame(s) 122-123. (Reel 5)
    - Gibbs, Georgia
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 124, So Ends the Night. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 791, So Ends the Night; 6, Muriel Smith. (Reel 11)
    - Gibson, Althea
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 125-129; 606, Hedda Hopper. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 11-15, Horse Soldiers. (Reel 6)
    - Gibson, D. Parks, Frame(s) 130-131. (Reel 5)
    - Gibson, Gertrude
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 132, The Press. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 693, The Press. (Reel 10)
    - The Gift, Frame(s) 133, Carl Byrd. (Reel 5)
    - Gigi, Frame(s) 134. (Reel 5)
    - Gilden, Richard, Frame(s) 135, The Black Klansman. (Reel 5)
    - Gildersleeves's Ghost, Frame(s) 136, Nicodemus Stewart. (Reel 5)
    - Gillespie, Dizzy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 402-429, Ray Charles; 601, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 95; 160-164, The Cool World; 418, Miles Davis. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 137. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 268, Jazz Scenes. (Reel 6)
    - Gillespie, William, Frame(s) 137. (Reel 5)
    - Gilliam, Stu
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 138-139. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 674b, Pot Luckless. (Reel 10)
    - Gilmore, Birdie, Frame(s) 109-110, Delsarte Film Corporation. (Reel 4)
    - Gilpin, Charles S.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 117, Colored Players Film Corporation. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 525-529, Eureka Film Company. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 140-142; 569-575, Hearts In Dixie. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 255-279, Robert Levy. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 110-111, James Lowe. (Reel 8)
    - Giovanni, Sposi, Frame(s) 143, Carol Carter. (Reel 5)
    - The Girl Can't Help It, Frame(s) 144. (Reel 5)
    - Girl Crazy, Frame(s) 145, Louis Armstrong. (Reel 5)
    - Girls from Trinidad, Frame(s) 146, Shirley Bassey. (Reel 5)
    - The Girl He Left Behind, Frame(s) 147, Bernie Hamilton. (Reel 5)
    - A Girl in Every Port, Frame(s) 148. (Reel 5)
    - A Girl Named Tomiko, Frame(s) 149, Jackie Wilson. (Reel 5)
    - The Girl Nobody Knows, Frame(s) 150, Ena Hartman. (Reel 5)
    - The Girl Who Dared, Frame(s) 151, Willie Best. (Reel 5)
    - Glamour, Frame(s) 152, Louise Beavers. (Reel 5)
    - Glass Slipper, Frame(s) 158, James Bower. (Reel 5)
    - Gleaves, Abraham, Frame(s) 253, Green Pastures. (Reel 5)
    - The Glenn Miller Story, Frame(s) 159, Louis Armstrong, et al. (Reel 5)
    - Glenn, Roy, Frame(s) 153-155 *. (Reel 5)
    - Global Affair, Frame(s) 160, Francois Andre. (Reel 5)
    - Glory Alley, Frame(s) 161-162, Louis Armstrong. (Reel 5)
    - Glory Road, Frame(s) 156. (Reel 5)
    - Glory Tent, Frame(s) 163. (Reel 5)
    - Glover, Mildred, Frame(s) 157 (No Info concerning her). (Reel 5)
    - Go, Man, Go, Frame(s) 185. (Reel 5)
    - The Goddess, Frame(s) 164, Louise Beavers. (Reel 5)
    - Goden, Freemon (Amos), Frame(s) 72-73, Amos & Andy. (Reel 1)
    - Godfrey, George
      - unspecified, [No further description available]. (Reel 5, 165)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 187, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 34-36, Old Ironside. (Reel 10)
    - Godfrey, Sam
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 166, List of Films. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 101, Love Captive; 102, Love in Bloom. (Reel 8)
    - God's Little Acre, Frame(s) 167-168, Rex Ingram. (Reel 5)
    - God's Step-Children, Frame(s) 169. (Reel 5)
    - God's Trombone, Frame(s) 590-661, Negroes in theatre. (Reel 9)
    - Going Places, Frame(s) 170. (Reel 5)
    - Gold, Frame(s) 171, Quincy Jones. (Reel 5)
    - Gold Digger in Paris, Frame(s) 175, Eddie Anderson. (Reel 5)
    - Gold is Where You Find It, Frame(s) 172, Willie Best. (Reel 5)
    - Goldberg & Port, Incorporated, Frame(s) 174. (Reel 5)
    - Goldberg, Jacy, Frame(s) 173. (Reel 5)
    - Golden Boy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 261-284, Godfrey Cambridge. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 546-550, Lola Falana. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 176. (Reel 5)
    - The Golden Coach, Frame(s) 177. (Reel 5)
    - Golden Gate Quartet
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 178; 561; 579 Hit Parade and Hollywood Canteen. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 817, Song is Born. (Reel 11)
    - The Golden Ghettos, Frame(s) 179, Raymond St Jacques. (Reel 5)
    - The Golden Goose, Frame(s) 180, Dorothy Parker. (Reel 5)
    - The Golden Pearls of Progress, Frame(s) 181. (Reel 5)
    - Golden Strain, Frame(s) 182, George Reed. (Reel 5)
    - The Golden West, Frame(s) 183, Hattie McDaniel. (Reel 5)
    - Goldoni, Lelia, Frame(s) 184, Shadows. (Reel 5)
    - Gomez, Tommy, Frame(s) 299-300, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - Gone Are the Days, Frame(s) 186. (Reel 5)
    - Gone With the Wind, Frame(s) 187-199. (Reel 5)
    - Gonsalves, Paul, Frame(s) 247. (Reel 2)
    - Good & Naughty, Frame(s) 200, Tom Moore. (Reel 5)
    - Good Morning Judge, Frame(s) 203, Louise Beavers. (Reel 5)
    - Good Picture Corporation, Frame(s) 204. (Reel 5)
    - Good Times, Frame(s) 205, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 5)
    - Goodbye Broadway, Frame(s) 201, Willie Best. (Reel 5)
    - Goodbye My Lady, Frame(s) 202, Sidney Poitier, Louise Beavers. (Reel 5)
    - Goodwin, Robert L., Frame(s) 206-207. (Reel 5)
    - Goodwin, Ruby
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 442, Louise Beavers. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 208. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 160, The Intruder. (Reel 6)
    - Gor, Fred, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Gordon Huntley, Frame(s) 209, address. (Reel 5)
    - Gordon Productions, Frame(s) 210, James Edwards. (Reel 5)
    - Gordone, Charles, Frame(s) 412, 414, 597. (Reel 9)
    - Gordy, Barry, Frame(s) 12, 15. (Reel 4)
    - Gore and Igor, Frame(s) 211. (Reel 5)
    - Gorgas, Alice
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 167, The Brute. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 499, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
    - Goss, Bobby, Frame(s) 212, The Learning Tree. (Reel 5)
    - Gossett, Lou
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 213-214; 288, Bill Gunn. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 616, Mister Adams. (Reel 8)
    - Graham, Earle, Frame(s) 215. (Reel 5)
    - Grand National, Frame(s) 217. (Reel 5)
    - Grand Slam, Frame(s) 218, Maxie McCrea. (Reel 5)
    - Grandma Bernie Learns Her Letters, Frame(s) 216, 219, Sam Baker; 309, John Hall. (Reel 5)
    - Grant, Alfred
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 73-75, Deep is the Well. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 220. (Reel 5)
    - Grant, Arthur, Frame(s) 583, Hollywood Productions. (Reel 5)
    - Grant, Cy, Frame(s) 221. (Reel 5)
    - Grant, Earl
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 442, Louise Beavers. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 222-226. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 95-105, Imitation of Life: 603, Juke Box Jamboree. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 183, Tender is the Night. (Reel 12)
    - Graves, Jessie, Frame(s) 227, Son of Ingagi; 583, Hollywood Productions. (Reel 5)
    - Gray, Dobie, Frame(s) 228, Out of Sight. (Reel 5)
    - Gray, Harry, Frame(s) 229-230. (Reel 5)
    - Gray, Jane, Frame(s) 588-627, Birth of a Race. (Reel 1)
    - Grayson, Jessica
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 372, Cass Timberlane. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 231, Little Foxes. (Reel 5)
    - Great Dan Patch, Frame(s) 232, Clarence Muse. (Reel 5)
    - Great Farewell, Frame(s) 233, John Kitzmiller. (Reel 5)
    - The Great Lie, Frame(s) 234, Sam & Hattie McDaniel. (Reel 5)
    - The Great Train Robbery, Frame(s) 235, Sammy Davis, Jr. (Reel 5)
    - The Great White Hope
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, James Earl Jones; 289, Moses Gunn; 456, Hilda Haynes. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 193, Jack Johnson Story. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 129-134, Yaphet Kotto. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 423, Negro boxers. (Reel 9)
    - The Great Ziegfield, Frame(s) 237, Lena Horne. (Reel 5)
    - The Greatest Sin, Frame(s) 238, distribution. (Reel 5)
    - The Greatest Story Ever Told, Frame(s) 239-241. (Reel 5)
    - Greaves, William
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 342; 571, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 826, Wealth of a Nation. (Reel 12)
    - Green, Bene
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 243. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 123. (Reel 7)
    - The Green Berets, Frame(s) 246-247, Raymond St. Jacques. (Reel 5)
    - Green, Cora, Frame(s) 661, Moon Over Harlem. (Reel 8)
    - Green, Ed
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 53-54, Deanwood Pictures. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 244. (Reel 5)
    - Green, Joe, Frame(s) 245, I Passed For White. (Reel 5)
    - Green Mansions, Frame(s) 251, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 5)
    - Green, Otis
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 251-252; 343, Handle With Care; 564, Hold Back the Night. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 51, Sunrise at Campebello. (Reel 12)
    - Green Pastures
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 253. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 365, playbill; 371-377, cast members; 590-661, Negroes in the theatre. (Reel 9)
    - Green, Rueben, Frame(s) 254. (Reel 5)
    - Greene, Laura
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 255. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 708, Slave Mutiny. (Reel 11)
    - Green-Eyed Blond, Frame(s) 248, Tommie Moore. (Reel 5)
    - Green-Eyed Monster
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 249-250. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 10, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Greenlee, Sam, Frame(s) 414. (Reel 9)
    - Greenwich Village, Frame(s) 257, The Four Step Brothers. (Reel 5)
    - Greenwood, Rene, Frame(s) 258. (Reel 5)
    - Gregory, Dick
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 235, Assault on a Queen. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 263, Godfrey Cambridge. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 259-263. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 714, Night Song. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 65-66, Sweet Love, Bitter; 404, Twilight of Honor. (Reel 12)
    - Gregory, Guy, Frame(s) 264. (Reel 5)
    - Grey Hat, Frame(s) 265. (Reel 5)
    - Grier, Roosevelt
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 253, Hullabaloo television show. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 266. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 666, Vini, Vidi, Vici. (Reel 12)
    - Griffin, Bessie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 350, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 267. (Reel 5)
    - Griffith, Douglas, Frame(s) 27, House Behind the Cedar. (Reel 6)
    - Griffith, Ernest, Frame(s) 129, the Inevitable. (Reel 6)
    - Griffin, L'Tanya, Frame(s) 268. (Reel 5)
    - Griner, Lawrence, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Guess Who's Coming to Dinner, Frame(s) 153, Roy Glenn; 269-282. (Reel 5)
    - A Guide for the Married Man, Frame(s) 283, Pat Sides. (Reel 5)
    - Guilford, Wilbur L., Frame(s) 401, Daughter of the Congo. (Reel 3)
    - Guilty as Hell, Frame(s) 284, Oscar Smith. (Reel 5)
    - The Gun, Frame(s) 285. (Reel 5)
    - Gun at Batasi, Frame(s) 291. (Reel 5)
    - Gun Packer, Frame(s) 286, Raymond Turner. (Reel 5)
    - Gunga Din, Frame(s) 287. (Reel 5)
    - Gunn, Bill
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 288. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 153, The Interns. (Reel 6)
    - Gunn, Moses, Frame(s) 289. (Reel 5)
    - Gunpoint, Frame(s) 290, Jeff Burton. (Reel 5)
    - Guns of the Magnificent 7, Frame(s) 293, Bernie Casey, Frank Silvera. (Reel 5)
    - Gunsaulus Mystery
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 3, Robert Abrams. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 294. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 392-562, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
    - Guyse, Sheila
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 26, Boy What a Girl. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 296-297; 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Gypsy Colt, Frame(s) 298, Jester Hairston. (Reel 5)
  - H
    - Hairston, Jester, Frame(s) 300-305 *. (Reel 5)
    - Hairston, William
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 306, Take the High Ground. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 107. (Reel 12)
    - Half an Angel, Frame(s) 307, Joyce Bryant. (Reel 5)
    - Hall, Adelaide
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 145, Brown Buddies; 556, Berry Brothers. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 247, 249, Cab Calloway. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 514, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Hall, Beulah
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 342, Lincoln Motion Picture; 693-709, Realization of Negro 710-715, Trooper of Troop K. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 205, Rare Photo. (Reel 9)
    - Hall, Iris, Frame(s) 308. (Reel 5)
    - Hall, John, Frame(s) 309, Grandma Bernie Learns Her Letters. (Reel 5)
    - Hall Johnson Choir
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Cabin in the Sky. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 170, Dimples; 619, Joel Fluellen. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 467, Hearts Divided. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 444, Hall Johnson. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 23, Lost Horizons. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 245, My Old Kentucky Home. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 61, Swannee River; 1097, Zenobia. (Reel 12)
    - Hall, Juanita
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 276-277, House of Flowers. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 310-316; 44, Hawaii. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 828-855, South Pacific. (Reel 11)
    - Hallelujah
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 229, Harry Gray; 317-321; 455, Daniel Haynes. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 284, Eva Mae Jessye. (Reel 6)
    - The Hallelujah Trail, Frame(s) 322, John Gay. (Reel 5)
    - Halls Book Mart, Frame(s) 418-422, Negro book dealers. (Reel 9)
    - Halls of Anger, Frame(s) 742-754, Calvin Lockhart. (Reel 7)
    - Hamile (Hamlet), Frame(s) 323. (Reel 5)
    - Hamilton, Bernie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 252, Lillian Cumber. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 324-332 *. (Reel 5)
    - Hamilton, Chico
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 400-429, Ray Charles. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 333. (Reel 5)
    - Hamilton, George W.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 73-75, Deep is the Well. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 334. (Reel 5)
    - Hamilton, Jimmy, Frame(s) 347, jam session. (Reel 2)
    - Hamilton, Josie, Frame(s) 10, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Hamilton, Kim, Frame(s) 335-336. (Reel 5)
    - Hamilton, Kipp, Frame(s) 664, Never So Few. (Reel 9)
    - Hamilton, Lynn, Frame(s) 395. (Reel 9)
    - Hamlet and Three Eggs, Frame(s) 337, Josephine Premice. (Reel 5)
    - Hampton, Lionel
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 68, America By Night. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 677, Force of Impulse. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 338-341; 559, History of Jazz. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 572, The Midas Run. (Reel 8)